There are many ways to see the same story
Battle for Haditha is a action, adventure, drama
film directed by Nick Broomfield.
An investigation of the massacre of 24 men, women and
children in Haditha, Iraq allegedly shot by 4 U.S.
Marines in retaliation for the death of a U.S.
Marine killed by a roadside bomb.
The movie follows the story of the Marines of Kilo Company, an Iraqi
family, and the insurgents who plant the roadside bomb.
Cpl. Matthews, played by Matthew Knoll.
Cpl. Ramirez, played by Elliott Ruiz.
Sgt. Ross, played by Eric Mehalacopoulos.
Cpl. Marcus, played by Nathan De La Cruz.
Capt. Sampson, played by Andrew McLaren.
Pfc. Cuthbert, played by Jase Willette.
Battle for Haditha is a 2007 drama film directed by British
director Nick Broomfield based on the Haditha killings.
Dramatising real events using a documentary style, Battle for
Haditha is Broomfield's follow up to Ghosts.
The film was aired on Channel 4 in the UK on 17 March 2008.
The film explores themes of circumcision, grenade, marine, attack, iraq war.
The tone is emotional.